Guide to the Stuart Stein papers, [ca. 1960-1995]
Stein, Stuart papers, [ca. 1960-1995]
- Series III. College of Architecture, Art & Planning
  - Department of City and Regional Planning
    - Curriculum
      - Course Materials
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Journal of John Finnecy, Dryden Elementary, May 22, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 58)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Journal of Gary L. Lapera, Belle Sherman Elementary, May 15, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 59)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Journal of Christine J. May, Belle Sherman Elementary I., 1985 (Box 4, Folder 60)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Journal of Christine J. May, Belle Sherman Elementary II., 1985 (Box 4, Folder 61)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Journal of Christine J. May, Belle Sherman Elementary III., 1985 (Box 4, Folder 62)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Library - Annotated Bibliograph of Materials, Spring 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Notes (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Photographs & Negatives (Box 5, Folder 3)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Photographs, Spring 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Rochester, N.Y. (Box 5, Folder 5)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Slides, Belle Sherman (Box 5, Folder 6)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Student Lesson Plan (Box 5, Folder 7)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Student Maps (Box 5, Folder 8)
        - CRP 556: Built Environment Education Workshop - Workshop for Teachers (Box 5, Folder 9)
        - CRP 557: Small-Town Community Design Workshop & CRP 758: Workshop in Urban Development Planning I. (Box 5, Folder 10)
        - CRP 557: Small-Town Community Design Workshop & CRP 758: Workshop in Urban Development Planning II. (Box 5, Folder 11)
        - CRP 557: Small-Town Community Design Workshop, Fall 1979 & Spring 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
        - CRP 557: Small-Town Community Design Workshop, Fall 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
        - CRP 557: Small-Town Community Design Workshop - Articles (Box 5, Folder 14)
        - CRP 557: Small-Town Community Design Workshop - Course Work Typing & Memos - Stein (Box 5, Folder 15)
        - CRP 557: Small-Town Community Design Workshop - Moravia, N.Y. - Dom Pedulla, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 13)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Norwich, N.Y. (Box 5, Folder 16)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Geneva, N.Y. (Box 5, Folder 17)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Tompkins/Ithaca Bikeways (Box 5, Folder 18)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Lansing Town/Village (Box 5, Folder 19)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Rochester, N.Y. (Box 5, Folder 20)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Rochester, N.Y. - Cornhill (Box 5, Folder 21)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Rochester, N.Y. - "Cornhill Neighborhood Vacant Municipal Land Study", February 1993 (Box 5, Folder 22)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Rochester, N.Y. - Silver Stadium Neighborhood (Box 5, Folder 23)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Rochester, N.Y. - Silver Stadium Neighborhood (Box 5, Folder 24)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop, Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Ithaca, N.Y. CBD, Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 26)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Owego, N.Y., Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Groton, N.Y., Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 28)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Ecovillage, Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 29)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Tompkins County ADA/Transit, Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 30)
        - CRP 558: City and Regional Planning Workshop - Springport, N.Y., Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 31)
        - CRP 561: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 32)
        - CRP 563 - Article (Box 5, Folder 33)
        - CRP 570: City and Regional Planning Workshop, Fall 1975 (Box 5, Folder 34)
        - CRP 571: Workshop in Latin American Planning, Fall 1980 (Box 5, Folder 35)
        - CRP 572: Program Planning & Community Action Groups - Student Work (Box 5, Folder 36)
        - CRP 572: Program Planning & Community Action Groups - Notes & Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 37)
        - CRP 572: Program Planning & Community Action Groups - Class Description, Objective, Goals, Etc. (Box 5, Folder 38)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop (Box 5, Folder 39)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 40)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Arts Quadrangle National Register Nomination (Box 5, Folder 41)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Elmira Project (Box 5, Folder 42)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Air Photos of Elmira Area, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 43)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Johnston Street (Box 5, Folder 44)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Ithaca, N.Y., Spring 1972 (Box 5, Folder 45)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Outline of Text (Box 5, Folder 46)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Planning Study of the Mynderse/Clinton Street Area, Village of Seneca Falls, N.Y., December 1976 (Box 5, Folder 47)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Scrapbook I. (Box 5, Folder 48)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Scrapbook II. (Box 5, Folder 49)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Scrapbook III. (Box 5, Folder 50)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Scrapbook IV. (Box 5, Folder 51)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Slides, Fall 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Slides (Corning, Lansing, Trumansburg, Dryden, Elmira, Interlaken & Ovid) I. (Box 6, Folder 2)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Slides (Corning, Lansing, Trumansburg, Dryden, Elmira, Interlaken & Ovid) II. (Box 6, Folder 3)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Student Papers, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Student Papers - Case Studies, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Student Papers - Case Studies, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - CRP 575: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop - Summary, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
        - CRP 575: Workshop in Urban Renewal Housing, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
        - CRP 580 - Student Papers (Box 6, Folder 9)
        - CRP 614: Neighborhood and Community Theory (Box 6, Folder 10)
        - CRP 629: Methods and Techniques of Urban Transportation Planning (Box 6, Folder 11)
        - CRP 641: Field Problem/Project (Box 6, Folder 12)
        - CRP 648: Federal Housing Program - Guest Lecturer's & Class Outlines, Fall 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
        - UPD 651 - "The Kawaida Controversy: A Case Study" by Ralph Waller, January 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
        - CRP 654: Built Environment Education Workshop (Box 6, Folder 15)
        - CRP 659: Alumni Seminar, Fall 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
        - CRP 701: Work Study Program I. (Box 6, Folder 17)
        - CRP 701: Work Study Program II. (Box 6, Folder 18)
        - CRP 701: Work Study Program III. (Box 6, Folder 19)
        - CRP 718: Workshop in City and Regional Planning - Local Economic Analysis (Box 6, Folder 20)
        - CRP 718: Civil Defense Proposed Project - Correspondence File I., 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 21)
        - CRP 718: Civil Defense Proposed Project - Correspondence File II., 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 22)
        - CRP 740 - Assorted Lecture Notes & Maps, Spring 1965 (Box 6, Folder 23)
        - CRP 742: Field Problem - Elmira / Elmira Urban Area Plan - Student Projects I., Fall 1964, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 24)
        - CRP 742: Field Problem - Elmira / Elmira Urban Area Plan - Student Projects II., Fall 1964, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
        - CRP 759: Built Environment Education Workshop, Spring 1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
        - CRP 779: Special Topics in Planning for Developing Regions, Spring 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
        - CRP 779: Special Topics in Planning for Developing Regions - Latin American Seminar - Case Study Outlines, Spring 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
        - CRP 779: Special Topics in Planning for Developing Regions - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 29)
        - CRP 779: Special Topics in Planning for Developing Regions - Student Papers, Spring 1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
        - CRP 779: Special Topics in Planning for Developing Regions - Student Papers, Fall 1979 (Box 6, Folder 31)
        - CRP 779: Special Topics in Planning for Developing Regions - Student Papers, Fall 1979 (Box 6, Folder 32)
        - CRP 779: Special Topics in Planning for Developing Regions - Student Papers, Fall 1979 (Box 6, Folder 33)
        - CRP 779: Special Topics in Planning for Developing Regions - Student Papers, Fall 1980 (Box 6, Folder 34)
        - CRP 790: Colloquium - Posters & Announcements I., [Fall 1988] (Box 6, Folder 35)
        - CRP 790: Colloquium - Posters & Announcements II., [Fall 1988] (Box 6, Folder 36)
        - CRP 790: Colloquium I., Fall 1988 (Box 6, Folder 37)
        - CRP 790: Colloquium II., Fall 1988 (Box 6, Folder 38)
        - CRP 878 - Student Papers, Spring 1981 (Box 6, Folder 39)
        - CRP 879: Int. Studies Plag. in Dev. Nations (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Course Schedules & Information
        - Catalog Changes, 1972, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 1)
        - Course Information (Box 7, Folder 2)
        - Course Schedules, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous Student Work & Course Material
        - Stein's Course Work Typing (Box 7, Folder 4)
        - Stuart Stein: Course Syllabus (Box 7, Folder 5)
        - Stuart Stein: Notes (Box 7, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous Class Handouts (Box 7, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous Maps (Box 7, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 7, Folder 9)
        - Thesis Approval (Box 7, Folder 10)
        - Thesis Project - Mark Wert (Box 7, Folder 11)
        - Dissertation Analysis Pre-Approval - Angelina Castro-Diaz (Box 7, Folder 12)
        - MA Thesis - Bob Woodworth (Box 7, Folder 13)
        - Amsterdam, [N.Y.]/Original Copy, December 1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
        - Amsterdam, N.Y. (Box 7, Folder 15)
        - Bath, N.Y. (Box 7, Folder 16)
        - Corning, [N.Y.]: Case Study - Drafts I. (Box 7, Folder 17)
        - Corning, [N.Y.]: Case Study - Drafts II. (Box 7, Folder 18)
        - Peter Finch - Elmira, [N.Y.] (Box 7, Folder 19)
        - [Greene, N.Y.] (Box 7, Folder 20)
        - Diehl, James (Box 7, Folder 21)
        - Dyer, Kerry (Box 7, Folder 22)
        - Foertsch, Andrea (Box 7, Folder 23)
        - Fuenmayor, Antonio J. (Box 7, Folder 24)
        - Kiss, Laszlo (Box 7, Folder 25)
        - Marsh, Vincent Scaramuzzo (Box 7, Folder 26)
        - Nishio, Hisamitsu (Box 7, Folder 27)
        - Phillips, Peter H. (Box 7, Folder 28)
        - Rowe, Kevin Christian (Box 7, Folder 29)
        - Schuchman, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 30)
        - Witten, Jonathan Douglas (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Faculty & Staff
      - Faculty Resumes (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Faculty Applications (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Faculty Meetings: Minutes (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Stein, Stuart W. - Biographical Information (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Stein, Stuart W. - Curriculum Vita (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Stein, Stuart W. - English Speaking Union: Churchill Traveling Fellowship, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Stein, Stuart W. - Record of Travel (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - Stein, Stuart W. - Sabbatic Leave Material (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Stein, Stuart W. - Student Advisory (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Boyar, Wesley V. (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Czamanski, Stanislaw I. (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Czamanski, Stanislaw II. (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Czamanski, Stanislaw III. (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Czamanski, Stanislaw - Res. Proposals (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Gentili, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Gray, Keith (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Hammerman, Howard I. (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Hammerman, Howard II. (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Hammerman, Howard III. (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Mirins, Leonard (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Nelkin, Dorothy I. (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Nelkin, Dorothy II. (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Nelkin, Dorothy III. (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - Reps, [John W.] (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Toomey, Michael (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - Werbizky, Tatiana G. - Curriculum Vita (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Financial Aid, Scholarships, Fellowships, etc.
      - CitiBank/Marine Midland: Student Funding (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Division of Historical and Anthropological Services: Historic Site Research Stipend, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Cornell National Scholar Nomination Information: Outstanding Applicants (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Davis-Minority Grad. Funding I. (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Davis-Minority Grad. Funding II. (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Davis-Minority Grad. Funding III. (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - LIU Memorial Award (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Mellon Fellowship (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Work Study Program - Rochester (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Work Study, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Work Study, Summer 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Financial Records
      - Financial Records (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Financial Records (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Active Research Projects & Training Grants (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Bookstore Billing Statements/Receipts (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Budget Matters (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Dept. Bgt. Req., October 1970, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Analysis Statements, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Monthly Operating Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Project Accounts & Contracts (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Project Accounts & Contracts (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - URS-CFCU Account (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Monthly Operating Schedules, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Publications, Papers, & Reports
      - Community Development Management and Reorganization Proposals, January 1979 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - An Environmentally Loaded Version of the Community Land Use Game, June 1, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - How Much Does the Review Planner Do?, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - "Requiem for Zoning" delivered at the National Planning Conference, April 7 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - International Studies in Planning - Annual Report, May 1980 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Career Histories of Cornell Planning Graduates: A Preliminary Report by Pierre Clavel, April 15, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Cornell Planning Newsletter, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Projects, Programs & Proposals
      - Highway Impact - Appalachia OPS, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Appalachia - Highway Fieldwork, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Banarsi Kambo Seminar, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Binghamton School District - Environmental Education (HEW) Proposal (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Bowers Foundation - Traveling Preservation Exhibit (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Community Design Assistance Program: Program Funding, 1982, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Community Design Assistance Program I., 1981-1984, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Community Design Assistance Program II., 1981-1984, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Community Design Assistance Program III., 1981-1984, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Community Design Assistance Program, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Community Design Assistance Program: Dresden-Yates County (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Community Design Assistance Program: Identity Survey, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Community Design Assistance Program: Application, Information, & Resumes, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Community Service Program: Boyar (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - Community Service Program: Clippings (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - Community Service Program: Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Community Service Program: Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - Consultant Services - List of Requests (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Ellis L. Phillips Foundation: Program in Environmental Education (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Ellis L. Phillips Foundation: Program in Environmental Education (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Ellis L. Phillips Foundation: Program in Environmental Education - Photographs & Negatives (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - "Environmental Education 1975" with LeGrace Benson (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Environmental Education - Corning, N.Y., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Higher Education Planning & Administration Program Proposal (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Historic Preservation Planning Program Proposal (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Interstate 88 - Susquehanna River Project (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Ithaca High School Project (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Ithaca High School Project (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Ithaca High School Project - Lecture Notes, Exercises, Etc. (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Latin American Program - Development (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Latin American Program - Guatemala (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Latin American Program - Haiti (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Latin American Program - Mexico (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Latin American Program - Puerto Rico (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Latin American Program - Puerto Rico (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Latin American Program - Sao Paulo University: Architecture & Urbanism Research - Photography Exhibition (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Latin American Program - Trinidad (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Latin American Program - Trinidad: Chaguaramas (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - Latin American Program - Venezeula: Institute of Urbanism - Omar Hernandez, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Luce Scholars Program, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Miscellaneous Projects & Proposals, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - New York City Summer Internship Program, Before 1970 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - New York City Summer Internship Program, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - New York City Summer Internship Program, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - New York City Summer Internship Program, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - New York City Summer Internship Program - Job Development, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - New York City Summer Internship Program - Internship Proposal, 1984-1985, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - New York City Summer Internship Program, Before 1987 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - New York State Senate Internship Program (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - Open Proposal Files (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Parks (Box 8, Folder 79)
      - Parks (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Parks Symposium (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Parks Symposium - Mailing Lists I. (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Parks Symposium - Mailing Lists II. (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Parks Symposium - Mailing Lists - Sympos Attendees (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Parks Symposium - Proceedings (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Parks Symposium - Souvenirs I. (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Parks Symposium - Souvenirs II. (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Parks Symposium (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Parks Symposium, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Cornell-Rochester Fieldwork Project Proposal, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Program Development Proposal - Rochester Field Program, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Research Proposals (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Research Proposals, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Research Proposal - Water Resources (Rochereau), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Roberts Hall Complex (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Building Space Projections I., 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Building Space Projections II., 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - CRP Space Needs I. (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - CRP Space Needs II. (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - CRP Space Needs- Perreault Visit - Space Estimates AAP, October 23-24, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - CRP Space Needs- Perreault, Maurice (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Summer Institute - Historic Preservation Planning, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Summer Institute - Small Town Revitalization Workshop, June 23-25, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Summer Institute - Small Town Revitalization Workshop, 1982, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Summer Institute - Design for the Downtown, June 22-25, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Summer Institute - Design for the Downtown, June 20-23, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Summer Institute - Design for the Downtown, June 20-22, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - SUNY Buffalo visit & lecture (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Understanding the Man-Made Environment (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Correspondence, Notes & Information (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Rochester - Phone Numbers (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Proposal & Budget (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Ibero-American Action League, Rochester, N.Y. I., 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Ibero-American Action League, Rochester, N.Y. II., 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Ibero-American Action League, Rochester, N.Y. III., 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Rochester Community Development Center (CDC) (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Community Design Centers I. (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Community Design Centers II. (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, Greg Jones, September 22, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: Rochester Museum and Science Center, September 1970-May 1971 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Urban Planning Services Project: RIT's Metropolitan Center (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Urban and Regional Studies Program Proposal, Development I. (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Urban and Regional Studies Program Proposal, Development II. (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Urban and Regional Studies Symposium (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Undergraduate Program Proposal (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - University Year in ACTION - Proposal, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - University Year in ACTION - Proposal, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - University Year in ACTION - Various Programs, 1971-1975 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Youth Grant Project - Ithaca, N.Y. School District (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - Youth Grants - Blake, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Youth Grants - Mazin, April 2, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Professional Work
  - Blair and Stein Associates
    - Reports (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Reports (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Reports (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Reports (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Reports (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Reports (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Reports (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Reports (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Reports (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Other
    - Elmira, N.Y. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Elmira, N.Y.: A Framework Plan for Downtown Elmira, N.Y. by Stuart W. Stein (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Elmira, N.Y.: Evaluation of Alternate Routes, July 1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Ithaca, N.Y. (Box 10, Folder 13)